<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NotificationChannel</string>
    <string name="launch_dialog_activity">Launch Dialog Activity</string>
    <string name="launch_toast_activity">Launch Toast Activity</string>
    <string name="launch_notification_activity">Launch Notification Activity</string>
    <string name="launch_snackbar_activity">Launch Snackbar Activity</string>
    <string name="toast_duration">Toast Duration:</string>
    <string name="short_toast">Short</string>
    <string name="long_toast">Long</string>
    <string name="show_action_snackbar">Show Action Snackbar</string>
    <string name="show_regular_snackbar">Show Regular Snackbar</string>
    <string name="display_simple_dialog">Display Simple Dialog</string>
    <string name="display_date_picker">Display Date Picker</string>
    <string name="show_choice_dialog">Show Choice Dialog</string>
    <string name="show_custom_layout">Show Custom Layout</string>
    <string name="FirstNameHint">First name</string>
    <string name="LastNameHint">Last name</string>
    <string name="simple_notification">Show Simple Notification</string>
    <string name="large_notification">Show Large Notification</string>
    <string name="action_notification">Show Action Notification</string>
    <string name="notification_news">This activity was launched as the result of a Notification</string>
    <string name="long_msg">This is a notification style that can contain a large amount of text. It works really well when you have a large amount of information
    to display in the notification area and want the user to be able to expand the message to see all of the content.</string>


    <string name="more_info">Info</string>
    <string name="contact_me">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="about_it">About it</string>
    <string name="about_it_info">This application is a demo for different ways to user communication and was created in kotlin more info
        you can visit the repository</string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright (c) 2020 Anel_CC and CherryApps

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.</string>
</resources>
